COVID-19 Pandemic Collection MS269
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Web crawls, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000182; 365 Web sites
  - How colleges, hospitals and cities can work together to save lives, 2020-04-13; MS269.000272; PBS NewsHour; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: By us, for us, 2020-04-13; MS269.000273; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Health Service transitions to telemedicine, continues COVID-19 testing, 2020-04-13; MS269.000274; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to Make Residence Halls Available to Local Hospitals and Host Cities, 2020-04-13; MS269.000275; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University offers tools, guidance to encourage universities to help relieve strain on nation's healthcare system, 2020-04-13; MS269.000276; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - University to house medical staff, patients in dorms, 2020-04-13; MS269.000277; Boston Business Journal; 1 Web sites
  - A Brief Update on Fall 2020, 2020-04-21; MS269.000278; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Guidance for the Fletcher Community, 2020-04-21 -- 2020-09-15; MS269.000279; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts must continue trend of empathy for students in face of new academic challenges, 2020-04-21; MS269.000280; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts must reflect on past and future needs of international students amidst crises, 2020-04-21; MS269.000281; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts sets moral example by providing full wages amid COVID-19 pandemic, 2020-04-21; MS269.000282; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - How Tufts Hillel Is Building Community Amid COVID-19, 2020-04-21; MS269.000283; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Impact of the pandemic on university finances and operations, 2020-04-21; MS269.000284; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Jumbo Days to Jumbo Month: Tufts Admissions creates virtual experience for Class of 2024, 2020-04-21; MS269.000285; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Open Society University Network and Talloires Network Launch COV-AID in Response to COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020-04-21; MS269.000286; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Pitching in to Create a New Kind of Safe Mask, 2020-04-21; MS269.000287; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Student journalism adapts, innovates during campus closures, 2020-04-21; MS269.000288; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tisch Library accommodates remote learning with expanded virtual resources, 2020-04-21; MS269.000289; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Introduces SAT & ACT Test-Optional Admissions Policy, 2020-04-21; MS269.000290; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to pilot test-optional admissions in 3-year trial, 2020-04-21; MS269.000291; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Undeterred by pandemic, TCU elections intensify online, 2020-04-21; MS269.000292; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - 4/21/2020 Executive Order - Suspension of US Immigration, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000293; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - 4/22/2020 - Executive Order Suspending Entry of Certain Immigrant Visa Holders, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000294; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Clinical Trials for Drugs to Treat COVID-19 Now Underway, 2020-04-27; MS269.000295; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Registry, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-05-05; MS269.000296; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Support, 2020-04-27; MS269.000297; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Testing, 2020-04-27; MS269.000298; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 vs. Flu, 2020-04-27; MS269.000299; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings School Farm Donates Eggs to Food Banks, 2020-04-27; MS269.000300; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Current state of coronavirus, 2020-04-27; MS269.000301; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Donations during COVID-19, 2020-04-27; MS269.000302; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts must adopt alternatives to full-time online learning if fall semester proves unsafe, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000303; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Fact vs. Fiction: COVID-19, 2020-04-27; MS269.000304; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - GS-US-540-5773: A Phase 3 Randomized Study to Evaluate the Safety and Antiviral Activity of Remdesivir (GS-5734™) in Participants with Severe COVID-19, 2020-04-27; MS269.000305; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - GS-US-540-5774: A Phase 3 Randomized Study to Evaluate the Safety and Antiviral Activity of Remdesivir (GS-5734™) in Participants with Moderate COVID-19 Compared to Standard of Care Treatment, 2020-04-27; MS269.000306; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - How to talk to your children about coronavirus, 2020-04-27; MS269.000307; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Missed seasons and opportunities: How student-athletes are faring at home, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000308; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Recommendations for immune suppressed patients, 2020-04-27; MS269.000309; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Recovery Support during the COVID-19 Pandemic, 2020-04-27; MS269.000310; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Staying calm and strong during coronavirus, 2020-04-27; MS269.000311; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Students, DCA documenting moment in time during COVID-19, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000312; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Talking to your child about coronavirus, 2020-04-27; MS269.000313; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Testing frequently asked questions, 2020-04-27; MS269.000314; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts anticipates significant budget deficit from COVID-19 costs, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000315; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Medical Center Partners with Medically Home for COVID-19 Response, 2020-04-27; MS269.000316; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Medical Center's COVID-19 test (Chinese), 2020-04-27; MS269.000317; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University, Tufts Medical Center establish seed funding program for COVID-19 research, 2020-04-27 -- 2020-04-30; MS269.000318; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Works to Tackle Pandemic Challenges, 2020-04-27; MS269.000319; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - What is coronavirus?, 2020-04-27; MS269.000320; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Career Center Workshop Recap: April 22, 2020, 2020-05-04; MS269.000321; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - From New York to California, COVID-19 disrupts Tufts students, their lifestyles, 2020-05-04; MS269.000322; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Photos: A campus without students, 2020-05-04; MS269.000323; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to pay dining workers through May 9, 2020-05-04; MS269.000324; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID Survivor's Registry: FAQ, 2020-05-06; MS269.000325; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Convalescent (Recovered) Patient Registry, 2020-05-06; MS269.000326; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Convalescent (Recovered) Patient Registry, 2020-05-06; MS269.000327; 1 Web sites
  - Alumni Step Up to COVID-19 Challenges, 2020-05-12; MS269.000328; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19: The Tufts Community Responds, 2020-05-12; MS269.000329; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Scientists Turned Volunteers, 2020-05-12; MS269.000330; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Alumnus Donates 350,000 Procedure Masks to Tufts Medical Center, 2020-05-12; MS269.000331; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - A Time to Celebrate Achievement, 2020-05-20; MS269.000332; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Are Countries Ready to Exit COVID-19 Lockdowns?, 2020-05-20; MS269.000333; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Cartoon: It might be stormy now, but it can't rain forever, 2020-05-20; MS269.000334; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - 'Community will always matter': Group of Six continues to support students remotely, 2020-05-20; MS269.000335; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 puts hold on Peace Corps, Fulbright plans for graduating seniors, 2020-05-20; MS269.000336; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial Cartoon, 2020-05-20; MS269.000337; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts must address deficiencies within health system exposed by pandemic, 2020-05-20; MS269.000338; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: University financial support proves vital in response to COVID-19 economic crisis, 2020-05-20; MS269.000339; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Faculty react to wage and salary freeze, budget deficit, 2020-05-20; MS269.000340; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - From engineering masks to caring for patients, Tufts students fight COVID-19, 2020-05-20; MS269.000341; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Green Line Extension construction continues amid pandemic, 2020-05-20; MS269.000342; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - How Will COVID-19 Affect Public Spaces?, 2020-05-20; MS269.000343; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - International Center Updates on COVID-19, 2020-05-20; MS269.000344; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Libraries Shift to Digital Mode, 2020-05-20; MS269.000345; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Making College Decisions in Uncertain Times · Inside Admissions, 2020-05-20; MS269.000346; 1 Web sites
  - More than 140 community members told to quarantine due to single case of COVID-19, 2020-05-20; MS269.000347; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - New program provides grants to Tufts students for summer projects that address effects of COVID-19, 2020-05-20; MS269.000348; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Can public health and politics be balanced in the WHO?, 2020-05-20; MS269.000349; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Pandemic response opens new chapter in town-gown relations, 2020-05-20; MS269.000350; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - PETA calls on Tufts, other universities to end animal testing amid COVID-19 crisis, 2020-05-20; MS269.000351; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Q&A: Monaco outlines possible return in fall, reflects on turbulent year, 2020-05-20; MS269.000352; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate closes year with internal elections, 2020-05-20; MS269.000353; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Baby Needed Surgery ASAP. Then a Pandemic Got in the Way, 2020-05-20; MS269.000354; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tips for a (Virtual) Campus Visit You'll Remember · Inside Admissions, 2020-05-20; MS269.000355; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - Tisch College to continue celebration of 20th anniversary into spring 2021, 2020-05-20; MS269.000356; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Lends Campus Space to Food Relief Groups Facing Sudden Demand, 2020-05-20; MS269.000357; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts receives $4.7 million from CARES Act, $2.3 million to go to emergency financial aid, 2020-05-20; MS269.000358; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts-based researchers design model connecting hospitals, college residential halls, 2020-05-20; MS269.000359; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Using Artificial Intelligence to Help Diagnose COVID-19, 2020-05-20; MS269.000360; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - What we're doing · Inside Admissions, 2020-05-20 -- 2020-06-22; MS269.000361; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - When the Pandemic Struck, This Class Struck Back, 2020-05-20; MS269.000362; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - When You Can't Visit Campus: How to Get to Know a College Online · Inside Admissions, 2020-05-20; MS269.000363; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - 6 Ways Couples Can Resolve Conflict During the COVID-19 Crisis, 2020-05-29; MS269.000364; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - As Massachusetts prepares to re-open, a new analysis examines risks, rewards of "Test and Trace", 2020-05-29; MS269.000365; Tufts Public Health; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Resources for Farmers and Food Businesses, 2020-05-29 -- 2020-09-23; MS269.000366; New Entry Sustainable Farming Project; 1 Web sites
  - Farm and Food Resources for the COVID-19 pandemic, 2020-05-29 -- 2020-09-23; MS269.000367; New Entry Sustainable Farming Project; 1 Web sites
  - March 2020 Covid-19 Email, 2020-05-29 -- 2020-09-23; MS269.000368; New Entry Sustainable Farming Project; 1 Web sites
  - Tracking COVID-19 Behind Bars, 2020-05-29; MS269.000369; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Emergency Response Grants Offered to Community Nonprofits, 2020-05-29; MS269.000370; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Where Does the Economy Go from Here?, 2020-05-29; MS269.000371; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19: Information & Research Resources, 2020-05-31 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000372; Office of the Vice Provost; 1 Web sites
  - Navigating the Pandemic: Knowledge, Resilience, Civic Purpose and Engagement, 2020-06-11; MS269.000373; Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life; 1 Web sites
  - CoVERS: Coronavirus Epidemiological Research & Surveillance, 2020-06-11 -- 2020-09-03; MS269.000374; Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine; 1 Web sites
  - A Mask Invented to Protect Eyes Now Also Protects Lives, 2020-06-11; MS269.000375; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Alumni Lead through the COVID-19 Crisis, 2020-06-11; MS269.000376; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Are Countries Ready to Exit COVID-19 Lockdowns?, 2020-06-11; MS269.000377; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Boston Hospitals PSA: Childrens Trauma, 2020-06-11; MS269.000378; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Boston Hospitals PSA: Medical Emergencies, 2020-06-11; MS269.000379; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Can Pets Get or Spread COVID-19?, 2020-06-11; MS269.000380; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Celebrating EMS Week 2020, 2020-06-11; MS269.000381; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19: The Tufts Community Responds, 2020-06-11; MS269.000382; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Dealing with Conflict in Your Family in the Time of COVID-19: The Importance of Listening, 2020-06-11; MS269.000383; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Dealing with Fear and Anxiety with Djordje Koldzic, MD, 2020-06-11; MS269.000384; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Dean Karimbux's COVID-19 Update, 2020-06-11; MS269.000385; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Dear Tufts Students: We Hope These Messages Make You Smile, 2020-06-11; MS269.000386; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Finding the Rhythm of Remote Learning, 2020-06-11; MS269.000387; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Grief in Health Care During COVID-19 with Tamara Vesel, MD, 2020-06-11; MS269.000388; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - How COVID-19 Affects Farmers and the Food Supply Chain, 2020-06-11; MS269.000389; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - How the Body Battles COVID-19, 2020-06-11; MS269.000390; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - How Tufts Organized Hundreds of Virtual Volunteers Amid COVID-19, 2020-06-11; MS269.000391; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Innovation and Inspiration Kept Art Thriving, 2020-06-11; MS269.000392; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Managing Being Home With Kids Full-Time with Alexis Davis, LICSW, 2020-06-11; MS269.000393; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Mom recovered from COVID-19 reunited with her premature twins, 2020-06-11; MS269.000394; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - On the Front Lines with the Underserved, 2020-06-11; MS269.000395; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Pomp and (Extenuating) Circumstance, 2020-06-11; MS269.000396; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - PPE Instructions and Tips for Children | Floating Hospital for Children, 2020-06-11; MS269.000397; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Protecting Online Privacy While Fighting A Pandemic, 2020-06-11; MS269.000398; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Public Safety Rolling Rally for Healthcare Workers, 2020-06-11; MS269.000399; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Safe With Us: A Guide for Patients, 2020-06-11; MS269.000400; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Searching for Ways to Defeat COVID-19, 2020-06-11; MS269.000401; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Talking to Children about Their Family Member's Hospitalization: ICU, 2020-06-11; MS269.000402; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Talking to Children about Their Family Member's Hospitalization: PICU, 2020-06-11; MS269.000403; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Talking to your Kids about COVID-19 with Alexis Davis, LICSW, 2020-06-11; MS269.000404; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - The Lack of Affordable Housing Is Getting Worse, 2020-06-11; MS269.000405; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - The Right Way to Work From Home, 2020-06-11; MS269.000406; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - The Veterinarian-Humanitarian, 2020-06-11; MS269.000407; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tisch College Launches Webinar for Students on Navigating the Pandemic, 2020-06-11; MS269.000408; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts COVID Patient Discharge, 2020-06-11; MS269.000409; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts MC COVID-19 montage | "I Believe" by Adam Ezra Group, 2020-06-11; MS269.000410; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mutual Aid (Twitter), 2020-06-11 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000411; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Students Help Local Health Departments Respond to COVID-19, 2020-06-11; MS269.000412; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University COVID-19 Student and Community Support Webinar, 2020-06-11; MS269.000413; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Update on Resuming Campus-Based Activities, 2020-06-11; MS269.000414; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Update on university budget actions, 2020-06-11; MS269.000415; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - We're all in this Together with Floating Hospital, 2020-06-11; MS269.000416; Tufts Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - What Causes Stress in Us—and Animals?, 2020-06-11; MS269.000417; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Will Remote School and Work Break the Internet?, 2020-06-11; MS269.000418; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 information and resources, 2018-04-23 -- 2020-09-03; MS269.000419; Tufts Clinical and Translational Science Institute; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 and the IGL, 2020-06-22; MS269.000420; Tufts Global Leadership; 1 Web sites
  - Jumbo Athletics Covid-19 Information, 2020-06-22; MS269.000421; Department of Athletics; 1 Web sites
  - Medical students graduate Maine Track program during coronavirus, 2020-06-22; MS269.000422; Newscentermaine.com; 1 Web sites
  - Modeling the COVID Epidemic in Real Time with Joshua Cohen, 2020-06-22; MS269.000423; Tufts CTSI Professional Education; 1 Web sites
  - Quarantine Eats, 2020-06-22; MS269.000424; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Researchers Across Tufts Pivot to Fight COVID-19, 2020-06-22; MS269.000425; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - They Go Where They Are Needed, 2020-06-22; MS269.000426; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - When Mosquito and Tick Season Meets COVID-19, 2020-06-22; MS269.000427; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Why Is There a COVID-19 Gender Gap?, 2020-06-22; MS269.000428; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Info Hub, 2020-06-23 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000429; Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine; 1 Web sites
  - BREAKING: Tufts announces plans for fall semester, will invite students back to campus, 2020-06-25; MS269.000430; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Fall Plans for Tufts Announced, 2020-06-25; MS269.000431; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - International Center Updates on COVID-19, 2020-06-25 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000432; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Music is Medicine for the Soul, 2020-06-25; MS269.000433; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Update on Tufts' Fall Plans, 2020-06-25; MS269.000434; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - What a college professor thinks about campus prep for the coronavirus, 2020-07-06; MS269.000435; Boston.com; 1 Web sites
  - We All Scream for Livestreams, 2020-07-07; MS269.000436; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - The Priority Area Research Group on Equity in Health, Wealth, and Civic Engagement, 2020-07-29 -- 09-03-2020; MS269.000437; The Research Group on Equity in Health, Wealth and Civic Engagement; 1 Web sites
  - Alumni Respond to COVID-19's Call, 2020-07-29; MS269.000438; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - NESCAC cancels fall sports season, 2020-07-29; MS269.000439; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Only 57 percent of Americans say they would get a COVID-19 vaccine, 2020-07-29; MS269.000440; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Peek into Fall Academics at the School of Arts and Sciences and School of Engineering, 2020-07-29; MS269.000441; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Pre-orientation programs to be virtual, free of cost to all students, 2020-07-29; MS269.000442; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Responding to new visa guidelines for international students' attendance this fall, 2020-07-29; MS269.000443; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Spring's Online Transition Prepped the School of Dental Medicine for Fall, 2020-07-29; MS269.000444; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts students engage in civic projects through Tisch Student COVID Response Program, 2020-07-29; MS269.000445; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Supports International Students in Face of ICE Rule, 2020-07-29; MS269.000446; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Why People of Color Are Suffering More from COVID-19, 2020-07-29; MS269.000447; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Women, college graduates, Democrats more likely to self-isolate to reduce coronavirus risks, 2020-07-29; MS269.000448; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - As Universities Prepare To Bring Students Back, Some Turn To Mass Coronavirus Testing, 2020-08-10 -- 2020-08-12; MS269.000449; WBUR; 1 Web sites
  - Coming Together Amidst COVID-19: The Tufts Community Response, 2020-08-10; MS269.000450; Tufts Observer; 1 Web sites
  - For washing your hands, is it more effective to use soap and water or an alcohol-based sanitizer?, 2020-08-10; MS269.000451; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Health Service Updates Related to COVID-19, 2020-08-10 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000452; Tufts Student Services; 1 Web sites
  - How to Be Alone Without Feeling Lonely, 2020-08-10; MS269.000453; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - How Tufts Is Convening a Call for a National Nutrition Research 'Moonshot', 2020-08-10; MS269.000454; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Medford Mayor 'Concerned' Over Tufts Reopening Amid Rising Cases, 2020-08-10; MS269.000455; Medford, MA Patch; 1 Web sites
  - Medford Residents Concerned Over Tufts Reopening Plan, 2020-08-10; MS269.000456; Medford, MA Patch; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Tufts, take a look around, would you?, 2020-08-10; MS269.000457; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Parent company of Tufts Medical Center furloughs, cuts hours for 2,000 workers, 2020-08-10; MS269.000458; The Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - The Tele-Veterinarian Will See You Now, 2020-08-10; MS269.000459; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts announces fall 2020 move-in updates, 2020-08-10; MS269.000460; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts builds modular dorms for students with COVID-19 symptoms, 2020-08-10; MS269.000461; WCVB Boston; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Plans To Conduct 18K+ Coronavirus Tests A Week, 2020-08-10; MS269.000462; Medford, MA Patch; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts will stagger arrival times for fall students, require COVID-19 testing and quarantine, 2020-08-10; MS269.000463; The Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - What was it like to live through the pandemic, grandpa? University archives seek items that capture COVID-19 history, 2020-08-10; MS269.000464; The Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - Yes, the Air Was Better During Lockdown, 2020-08-10; MS269.000465; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Joint statement from Somerville and Medford mayors on Tufts reopening plan, 2020-08-12; MS269.000466; The Somerville Times; 1 Web sites
  - Somerville and Medford are pressing Tufts to reconsider its reopening plan, 2020-08-12; MS269.000467; Boston.com; 1 Web sites
  - Does Working from Home Actually Work?, 2020-08-14; MS269.000468; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Filling the Internship Vacuum by Coding for Good Causes, 2020-08-14; MS269.000469; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - How Does Art Change Our Perceptions of COVID-19?, 2020-08-14; MS269.000470; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Newsletter - Community Relations, 2020-08-14 -- 2020-09-18; MS269.000471; 1 Web sites
  - Pressure builds for Tufts to scale back on-campus experience amid coronavirus, more Massachusetts colleges reverse course, 2020-08-14; MS269.000472; Boston Herald; 1 Web sites
  - Somerville residents, city councilors want to see changes in Tufts' plan, 2020-08-14; MS269.000473; Somerville Journal; 1 Web sites